### FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

### Rakotoasimbola Fana

Paris | f.rakotoasimbola@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/fanamperantsoa-rakotoasimbola-36588915b/ | https://github.com/fanama

### **ABOUT ME**

I began my journey in computer science at a young age, crafting small games with Game Maker and RPG Maker. Now boasting over 5 years of experience, I excel in JavaScript, Golang, and Python across both front-end and back-end development domains. My adaptability to various technologies allows me to meet client needs and requirements effectively. Presently, I am on the lookout for a role in Research & Development that encapsulates both front-end and back-end facets.

### **EXPERIENCES**

### SFR, Fullstack Developer

(2023-today)

- Mission: Developed an API and to use multiple llm services.
- Technologies Used: React, Golang, NodeJS, Google Vertex, OpenAI.
- Objective: Created an API for agents to query assistance in natural language, enabling rapid response to user requests.

#### XXII CORE, Fullstack Developer

(2022, 4 months)

- Mission: Involved in the maintenance and development of a video analysis platform.
- Technologies Used: ReactJS, NodeJS, MongoDB.
- Objective: Enhanced the platform's real-time analysis capability for detecting objects or people in motion.

## Cliris / Dasia, Fullstack Developer

(2019-2022, 3 years)

- Mission: Focused on software and web development.
- Technologies Used: ReactJS, NodeJS, Golang, MySQL, MongoDB.
- Objective: Developed a software platform for real-time video stream analysis and various tools, including :
  - labelling tool for computer vision model training.
  - API for User management

## Aurera, Software Developer

(2019, 4 months)

- Mission: Developed a chatbot for the company's website.
- Technologies Used: NodeJS, Microsoft Azure.
- Objective: Engaged visitors through conversational AI, trained using Microsoft Azure's NLP services, as part of a digital transformation initiative.

### **EDUCATION**

SUPINFO, Master 2: Expert in Computer Science, Specialization: Web Development	Supinfo Paris (2017-2020)
Classe Préparatoire aux Grandes Ecoles, TSI Maths sup/spé	Lycée Raspail Paris (2015-
	2017)

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

E-anatra : A project aimed at improving education in Madagascar. Utilized Trello, Google Suite, Asana Clip Studio, and Photoshop JS

(Since Oct 2022)

Lamako: Worked as a web designer and developer for a startup promoting Malagasy culture through a board game. Used (2017-2019, 2 years) Photoshop and Clip Studio Paint

# SKILLS

Backend	Python, Flask, Golang, NodeJS
Frontend	JavaScript / TypeScript, ReactJS, Svelte, htmx, TailwindCSS
Database (BDD)	MySQL, MongoDB, Elasticsearch, RabbitMQ
Infrastructure / Cloud	Docker, Batch
Artificial Intelligence	Google Vertex, OpenAI, Mistral AI
Tools	Git, Jest, Cypress
Languages	French (Native)
	English (fluent)
	Malagasy (fluent)

1